fontcapture.com 2016-11-20

# YourFonts - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Updated: Thursday, September 3, 2009 (previous version can be found here)

#### Philosophy

We are only interested in collecting and retaining the information that is necessary to effectively run our business. We respect your right to keep your personal information private.

#### Uploaded Files and Generated Fonts

All uploaded files and generated fonts are stored on our servers for a maximum of 15 days. We never share personal information. Occasionally an attempt to generate a font fails, and then we might look into such problem to see if we can improve our font generation algorithm. So that's the only possible reason for us to use uploaded data, and even then it's only used to look into issues with our font generator. Although it makes us happy to see so many people pleased with their own custom fonts, we are by no means interested in the individual fonts generated through our service. We prefer to put time and effort in improving existing and developing new software and services.

#### E-mail

We will not sell your e-mail address, nor do we provide it to advertisers or mass marketers. In other words, you will never receive junk mail based on information you submit directly to us. You may remove yourself from our electronic mailing lists by following the directions included in each e-mail or at this page.

#### Outside Links

This website provides links to other Internet sites. We are not responsible for the content, products, services or privacy policies of these sites.

#### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

#### Assent

By using this website, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the website. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to these terms will signify that you accept the changes.

#### Questions or Comments

For additional questions, please contact our team using our contact form.

### Getting Started

 Print Template

 Complete Template

 Scan & Save Template

 Upload Template

 Preview Your Font

 Download

 Install & Use

* * *

**New: Signature Fonts**  
Make a font with up to 16 signatures through [Sigfonts.com](http://www.sigfonts.com/)

* * *

Subscribe to our newsletter or follow us on Twitter. Once or twice a year we'll send you a discount coupon, so join now!

* * *

**User Quotes (view all quotes)**  
---  
  
“My G'Ma passed about 6 months ago. She was remembered by all for the letters she wrote to others. Her eulogy was called Letters From Virginia. I spend over a month cutting and pasting individual letters of the alphabet to create a font name G'Ma. As I sit here in tears of joy (and tears of missing her), I now can see her writings whenever I want. Thank you for making this happen. I can't...” [more]

#### **Holly Sandy**

December 22, 2014  
  
Add your opinion about YourFonts.com. 

* * *
